RESUME

Name: Patel Parag Jayantilal

Address: B/79, Chitralekha Society,

Ajay Tenament Part-2,

Mahadev Nagar Tekra, Vastral Road,

Ahmedabad-382418

Mobile No.: 8320134512, 7265049524

E-mail I'd: paragpagtel2908483@gmail.com

A dynamic professional with expertise and accomplished experience of over 7.6 years in ITI(Electrical), 4.5 years in Bulk Line packaging machine operator in Zydus Cadila, 2 years experience in Inttas Pharmaceutical as CVC Line Machine Operator, 5 years in VI (Vodafone Idea) as in the post of store in charge and currently working in Sodexo India Service Private Limited as a post of an electrician.

Career Objective:

Intend to build my career in leading organization with committed and delicate working pattern, which will help to explore fully and realise my potential and willingness to work as a key player in challenging and creative environment.

Work Experience:

- 1. Man Industries India Ltd., Anjar, Gujarat
 - Position : Electrician
 - Duration: 20/09/2008 31/03/2009
- 2. Zydus Cadila Health Care Ltd., Moraiya, Ahmedabad
 - Position : **Tablet Line Machine Operator**
 - Duration: 01/04/2009 10/02/2014

3. Inttas Pharmaceuticals Ltd.

• Position : CVC Line Machine Operator

• Duration: 15/12/2014 – 08/08/2016

4. VI (Vodafone Idea)

• Position : **Store incharge**

• Duration: 2016 – 2021

5. Sodexo India Service Private Limited

• Position : **Electrician**

• Duration : 2021 - current

Academic Course:

Course	Board/University	Passing Year	Percentage
S.S.C	GSEB	2001	62.14
ITI Electrician	NCVT	2007	71.00
Electrical	State Council for Technical	2015	74.23
Communication	Education and Vocational		
	Training		

Computer Skill:

Proficient with the use of Windows, MS Office

and Internet Surfing

Course in computer society, DOEACE Society

Personal Details :-

Date of birth:29/08/1984

Marital Status: Married

Father's name : Jayantilal Patel

Gender: Male

Languages known: Gujarati, Hindi,

English Nationality : Indian

Hobbies: Listening Music, Travelling,

Driving Place of Stay: Ahmedabad

Signature
Parag Patel